BUCUR RADU

WEB DESIGNER



0730327737



radu.radubc@gmail.com



Bucharest



PROFILE

I am an experienced self-taught Designer bringing over 2 years of experience applying technical and creative abilities to diverse projects. Great wireframing, mocking up and prototyping skills, with efficiency in collaborating with artistic and project leadership to complete tasks according to deadline. A proactive person with great skills in problem solving.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design Freelance - 2021

Created visuals, graphic elements, designed applications based on client requirements.

UX/UI Designer intern - 2020

Agrocity / Bucharest

Learned Figma from scratch, design process, typography and colors, wireframing, user research, worked with developers.

UX/UI Team Leader - 2019

EESTEC / Bucharest

I supervised a team of three members with whom I worked at the design of Soft Skills Academy website. Worked closely with the developers to create the website.

Head Organiser Design Sprint 6 - 2019

EESTEC / Bucharest

I coordinated a team of 5, together we organised an international event, 5 days of workshop and working sessions on Adobe products (ex. Photoshop, Illustrator, XD etc.).

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020

Bachelor's Degree / Robotics
University Politehnica of
Bucharest

2012 - 2016

Baccalaureate / Informatics "Ienachita Vacarescu" National College, Targoviste

LANGUAGE

- Romanian
- English

SKILLS

- XD
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- After effects
- Figma
- HTML
- CSS
- AutoCAD

EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Team Leader - 2019

EESTEC / Bucharest

I supervised a team of three members with whom I worked on the design of an internal app designed to ease the member managing inside the association. Worked closely with the developers to create the application.

PR Responsible - 2018

EESTEC/ Bucharest

I was responsible for the PR of the 24h hackathon EESTEC Olympics, I gained experience in digital advertising campaigns, creating promo materials, designing a website.

VOLUNTEERING

EESTEC LC Bucharest - 2017 - Present

Alumnus Member

Very good organizational and teamwork skills gained by organizing events and working especially with the IT and PR departments.

EESTEC LC Bucharest - 2017 - 2020

Graphic Designer

Sketched and designed visuals based on requirements, received and gave feedback on different designs, used Illustrator, Photoshop to create graphic elements.

TOOLS

- Gitlab
- Jira
- Slack
- Trello

HOBBIES

- Hiking
- Photography
- Tech